[{"instructions":"Let's define a new operation +<sub>6</sub>. This operation will give us a way of combining two of the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5 to get another one of them back. To perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result. (That's why the operation is called +<sub>6</sub>.) <br /><br />For example, 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2, because 3 + 5 = 8, and 8 is bigger than 6, so we subtract 6, and 8 - 6 = 2. So 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2.<br /><br />Similarly, 1 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5, because 1 + 4 = 5, and 5 is less than 6 so we leave it alone.<br /><br />Click Continue when you're ready to move on.","rt":359647,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":1,"time_elapsed":378568,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Do you see how +<sub>6</sub> works? By subtracting 6 every time we get above 5, we ensure t hat when  we combine two numbers using +<sub>6</sub>, we only produce numbers between 0 and 5.<br /><br />Click Continue when you're ready to move on.","rt":13178,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":2,"time_elapsed":391746,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now try one on your own! What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"5","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["5"],"rt":6809,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":3,"time_elapsed":398565,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 3 because 4 + 5 = 9 and 9 - 6 = 3.","rt":57309,"trial_type":"feedb ack","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":4,"time_elapsed":455884,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["5"],"rt":6573,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":5,"time_elapsed":462467,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 5 because 3 + 2 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":1359,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":6,"time_elapsed":463826,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, an d then a dd the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["0"],"rt":4011,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":7,"time_elapsed":467837,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0 because 1 + 5 = 6 and 6 - 6 = 0.","rt":1530,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":8,"time_elapsed":469367,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2"],"rt":3573,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":9,"time_elapsed":472940,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 2 because 1 + 1 = 2 and 2 is less than 6.","rt":1240,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":10,"time_elapsed":474180,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3"],"rt":3505,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":11,"time_elapsed":477686,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Corre ct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 3 because 3 + 0 = 3 and 3 is less than 6.","rt":1031,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":12,"time_elapsed":478717,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2\n","2"],"rt":5118,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":13,"time_elapsed":483835,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 2 because 4 + 4 = 8 and 8 - 6 = 2.","rt":1410,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":14,"time_elapsed":485245,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What i s 1 +<su b>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["4\n","4"],"rt":5481,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":15,"time_elapsed":490727,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 4 because 1 + 3 = 4 and 4 is less than 6.","rt":26785,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":16,"time_elapsed":517512,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigge r, you s ubtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1"],"rt":2918,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":17,"time_elapsed":520438,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 1 because 4 + 3 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":1151,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":18,"time_elapsed":521590,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["5"],"rt":3168,"trial_type":"quest ion","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":19,"time_elapsed":524758,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 5 because 0 + 5 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":1273,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":20,"time_elapsed":526031,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1"],"rt":2425,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":21,"time_elapsed":528456,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 1 because 2 + 5 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":1400,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":22,"time_elapsed":529856,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"instructions":"Now we're going to discuss a couple special properties of this new operation, +<sub>6</sub> that we've learned. First, notice that the number 0 behaves in a special way under +<sub>6</sub>. Whenever we combine 0 with anything else, we get that same thing back. We'll say that 0 is the <i>identity</i> under +<sub>6</sub>, because when you combine it with something it gives you that identical thing back.","rt":36415,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":23,"time_elapsed":566271,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Now that we know 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>, we're going to make a new definition. We'll say that the <i>inverse</i> of a number is the element that you combine with it to produce the identity. For example, 5 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 0, so we say 1 is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>6</sub>, (remember 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</s ub>). Si milarly, 3 is its own inverse under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0.","rt":68400,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":24,"time_elapsed":634681,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! What is the inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2"],"rt":6246,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":25,"time_elapsed":640934,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub> is 2 because 4 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1207,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":26,"time_elapsed":642151,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the invers e of 1 u nder +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["5"],"rt":3143,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":27,"time_elapsed":645294,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub> is 5 because 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1058,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":28,"time_elapsed":646352,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3"],"rt":2970,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":29,"time_elapsed":649322,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub> is 3 because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1116,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":30,"time_elapsed":650438,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["4"],"rt":3132,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":31,"time_elapsed":653570,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub> is 4 because 2 +<sub>6</sub> 4  = 0, an d 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":71553,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":32,"time_elapsed":725123,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"6","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["6"],"rt":4872,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":33,"time_elapsed":730005,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. The inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub> is 0 because 0 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":47409,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":34,"time_elapsed":777425,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"instructions":"It is also possible to successively apply +<sub>6 </sub>,  and the operation can simply be performed starting with the left-most pair. For example, 2 +<sub>6</sub> 3 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 3.","rt":31065,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":35,"time_elapsed":808497,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"We have one last definition to learn today, using the successive operations we just learned. Let's start with an example. Under our operation +<sub>6</sub> we can make every other number using just 1: 2 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 3 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 4 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 5 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, and 0 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1. Because 1 can make every other element under +<sub>6</sub>, we say that 1 is a <i>generator</i> under +<sub>6</sub>. <br /><br /> However, 2 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, and  0 = 2 + <sub>6</sub> 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 2.","rt":145321,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":36,"time_elapsed":953828,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! Is 3 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"Yes","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Yes"],"rt":34681,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":37,"time_elapsed":988519,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 3 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 = 3, 0 = 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 4, or 5 using just 3.","rt":10276,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":38,"time_elapsed":998805,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is  5 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"No","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["No"],"rt":2027,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":39,"time_elapsed":1000835,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 5 is a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 5 = 5, 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 3 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 2 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 1 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, and 0 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, so you can make all of the numbers under +<sub>6</sub> using 5","rt":4950,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":40,"time_elapsed":1005785,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0 .10-0"},{"question":"Is 4 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["No"],"rt":2942,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":41,"time_elapsed":1008727,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 4, 2 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, and 0 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 4.","rt":1446,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":42,"time_elapsed":1010173,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 0 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["No"],"rt":20115,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":43,"time_elapsed":1030288,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 0 = 0, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 3, 4, or 5 using just 0.","rt":1174,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":44,"time_elapsed":1031472,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"instructions":"Now we are going to ask you some questions about a new operation, +<sub>9</sub>, on the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8. It works exactly like +<sub>6</sub>, except now after adding the two numbers you subtract 9 if your result is 9 or greater. <br /><br />Do you see how +<sub>9</sub> works just like +<sub>6</sub>? By subtracting 9 every time we get above 8, we ensure that when we combine two numbers using +<sub>9</sub>, we only produce numbers between 0 and 8.<br /><br  />We'll  give you one practice question with feedback to make sure you understand the new operation. After that, try to complete the remaining questions as accurately as possible.","rt":35615,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":45,"time_elapsed":1067087,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Practice: What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1\n","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1\n"],"rt":5544,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":46,"time_elapsed":1072639,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5 = 1 because 5 + 5 = 10 and 10 - 9 = 1.","rt":4548,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":47,"time_elapsed":1077187,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>9</sub> 3?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"6","response":"6","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["6"],"rt":4163,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":48,"time_elapsed":1081350,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 7 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2"],"rt":2486,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":49,"time_elapsed":1083836,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>9</sub> 8?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["0"],"rt":2385,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":50,"time_elapsed":1086221,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0 ","response":"0","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["0"],"rt":2305,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":51,"time_elapsed":1088527,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 6 +<sub>9</sub> 6?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3"],"rt":3103,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":52,"time_elapsed":1091630,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"instructions":"On the following question, and several others later in the HIT, we will ask you to explain how you got your answer. On these questions, you will be given one box for your answer to the question, and a second for your explanation. Please explain your thought process in as much detail as possible (at least one sentence, and more if you can).","rt":26833,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":53,"time_elapsed":1118463,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>9</sub> 1? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","explain":true,"explanation":"four plus one equals 5 which is less than 9","explanation_history":["4","for ","for","four pol","four po","four plus one equal ","four plus one equal","four plus one equas","four plus one equals 5 which is less than 9"],"response_history":["5"],"rt":29760,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":54,"time_elapsed":1148230,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 8 +<sub>9</sub> 4? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":true,"explanation":"eight plus four equals twelve subtract nine equals 3","explanation_history":["eight plus nine eq","eight plus nine e","eight plus nine ","eight pl us nine","eight plus nin","eight plus ni","eight plus n","eight plus four qu","eight plus four q","eight plus four eu","eight plus four equals twelve subtract nine equals 3"],"response_history":["3","3"],"rt":36697,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":55,"time_elapsed":1184934,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the identity under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":true,"explanation":"When 0 +9 any number it will equal that number until you get to 9","explanation_history":["When 0 +9 any number i","When 0 +9 any number it will equal that number until you get to 9"],"response_history":["0"],"rt":260519,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":56,"time_elapsed":1445460,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["4"],"rt":26663,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":57,"time_elapsed":1472123,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"7","response":"7","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["7"],"rt":2828,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":58,"time_elapsed":1474961,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"9","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["9"],"rt":9689,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":59,"time_elapsed":1484650,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of  3 under  +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"6","response":"6","explain":true,"explanation":"three plus six equals nine subtract nine equals zero. The inverse of a number under plusnine is the number which will make the operation equal to zero.","explanation_history":["three plusnine six eq","three plu","three pl","three p","three plus six equals nine subtract nine equals 0/ ","three plus six equals nine subtract nine equals 0/","three plus six equals nine subtract nine equals 0","three plus six equals nine subtract nine equals zero. The inverse of a number under plusnine is the number wi","three plus six equals nine subtract nine equals zero. The inverse of a number under plusnine is the number which will make the operation equal to zero."],"response_history":["6"],"rt":55482,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":60,"time_elapsed":1540132,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0 "},{"question":"Is 2 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"Yes","explain":true,"explanation":"numers zero thru 8 can be achieved by adding 2 plusnine over and over, ie 2 +9 2 = 4; 2 +9 2 +9 2 =6","explanation_history":["there is no way to make seven or ","2","a","num,b","num,","numers one thr","numers one th","numers one t","numers one ","numers one","numers on","numers o","numers zero throu","numers zero thro","numers zero thr","numers zero thu","numers zero thru 8 can be achieve by adding 2 plusnine","numers zero thru 8 can be achieve by adding ","numers zero thru 8 can be achieve by adding","numers zero thru 8 can be achieve by addin","numers zero thru 8 can be achieve by addi","numers zero thru 8 can be achieve by add","numers zero thru 8 can be achieve by ad","numers zero thru 8 can be achieve by a","numers zero thru 8 can be achieve by facto ring 2 a nd","numers zero thru 8 can be achieve by factoring ","numers zero thru 8 can be achieve by fact","numers zero thru 8 can be achieve by fac","numers zero thru 8 can be achieve by fa","numers zero thru 8 can be achieve by f","numers zero thru 8 can be achieve by ","numers zero thru 8 can be achieve by","numers zero thru 8 can be achieve b","numers zero thru 8 can be achieve ","numers zero thru 8 can be achieved by adding 2 plusnine over and over \nie ","numers zero thru 8 can be achieved by adding 2 plusnine over and over \nie","numers zero thru 8 can be achieved by adding 2 plusnine over and over \ni","numers zero thru 8 can be achieved by adding 2 plusnine over and over \n","numers zero thru 8 can be achieved by adding 2 plusnine over and over ","numers zero thru 8 can be achieved by adding 2 plusnine over and over, ie 2 =9 ","numers zero thru 8 can be achieved by adding 2 plusnine over and over, ie 2 =9","numers zero thru 8 can be achieved by adding 2 plusnine over and ove r, ie 2  =","numers zero thru 8 can be achieved by adding 2 plusnine over and over, ie 2 +0","numers zero thru 8 can be achieved by adding 2 plusnine over and over, ie 2 +92","numers zero thru 8 can be achieved by adding 2 plusnine over and over, ie 2 +9 2 = 4; 2 +9 2 + ","numers zero thru 8 can be achieved by adding 2 plusnine over and over, ie 2 +9 2 = 4; 2 +9 2 +9 2+","numers zero thru 8 can be achieved by adding 2 plusnine over and over, ie 2 +9 2 = 4; 2 +9 2 +9 2 +","numers zero thru 8 can be achieved by adding 2 plusnine over and over, ie 2 +9 2 = 4; 2 +9 2 +9 2 =6"],"response_history":["No","Yes"],"rt":430793,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":61,"time_elapsed":1970925,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 3 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","explain":true,"explanation":"there is no way to arrive at  1, 2, 4 , 5, 7, 8","explanation_history":["there is no way to arrive at 2, 4, 6","there is no way to arrive at 2, 4, 8","there is no way to arrive at 2, 4, 7","there is no way to arrive at 2, 4, 6","there is no way to arrive at 2, 4, 5","there is no way to arrive at 12, 4, 5","there is no way to arrive at 1,2, 4, 5","there is no way to arrive at 1, 2, 4, 5, 7, 8"],"response_history":["No"],"rt":178663,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":62,"time_elapsed":2149598,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"Yes","explain":true,"explanation":"adding 5 with the plusnine over and over again arrives at numbers 1-8","explanation_history":["adding 5 +9 5","adding ad","adding a","adding 5 with the plusnine over and over again arrives at numbers 1-8"],"response_history":["Yes"],"rt":194520,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":63,"time_elapsed":2344120,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 6 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","explain":true,"explanation":"one cannot arrive at all the numbers between 0-8 as answers when 6 is factored with plusnine","explanation_history":["one cannot arrive at all nt","one cannot arrive at all n","one cannot arrive at all the numbers between 0-8 as answers when 6 is factored with plusnine"],"response_history":["No"],"rt":105504,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":64,"time_elapsed":2449631,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"instructions":"Now we'd like to ask you some questions about +<sub>n</sub>, where n could be any postive counting number. For example, n could be 3, or n could be any other counting number you can think of. If you need  to write  the operation, you can use +_n, and your answers can include n to stand in for the arbitrary value if necessary.","rt":32411,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":65,"time_elapsed":2482042,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of 1 under +<sub>n</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-1","response":"1 +_n (n-1) = 0","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["n-1","n-","n","1","1 +_n (n-1) = 0"],"rt":146364,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":66,"time_elapsed":2628406,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of an element x under +<sub>n</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-x","response":"x +_n (n-x) =0","explain":true,"explanation":"i guessed","explanation_history":["i guessed"],"response_history":["1","x +_n (n-x) =0"],"rt":84712,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":67,"time_elapsed":2713118,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Is there a pattern to which elements are generators? How can you know if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub> without seeing whether it can make all the elements?.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"I am not that sophisticated. I make all the elements. You should advise me of this pattern ahead so that I can put it to use.","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["I am not that so","I am not that sophisticated. I make all the elements. You shoud","I am not that sophisticated. I make all the elements. You should advise me of this form","I am not that sophisticated. I make all the elements. You should advise me of this for","I am not that sophisticated. I make all the elements. You should advise me of this fo","I am no t that s ophisticated. I make all the elements. You should advise me of this f","I am not that sophisticated. I make all the elements. You should advise me of this pattern so tht ","I am not that sophisticated. I make all the elements. You should advise me of this pattern so tht","I am not that sophisticated. I make all the elements. You should advise me of this pattern so th","I am not that sophisticated. I make all the elements. You should advise me of this pattern so t","I am not that sophisticated. I make all the elements. You should advise me of this pattern so ","I am not that sophisticated. I make all the elements. You should advise me of this pattern so","I am not that sophisticated. I make all the elements. You should advise me of this pattern s","I am not that sophisticated. I make all the elements. You should advise me of this pattern ahead so that I can put it to use."],"rt":33360,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":68,"time_elapsed":2746478,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an odd number, it must be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["False"],"rt":18421,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":69,"time_elapsed":2764909,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an even number, it must not be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["False"],"rt":19521,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":70,"time_elapsed":2784443,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a divisor of n, that is, x must divide n eve nly, wit h no remainder.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"True","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["True"],"rt":20818,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":71,"time_elapsed":2805262,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a multiple of a divisor of n. Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"True","response":"True","explain":true,"explanation":"x=3 \nn=9","explanation_history":["x=3 \nn=9"],"response_history":["True"],"rt":96209,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":72,"time_elapsed":2901480,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"If an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is its inverse a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Always","response":"Sometimes","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Sometimes"],"rt":9791,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":73,"time_elapsed":2911278,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Sometimes","response":"Sometimes","explain":true,"explanation":"I guessed.","explanation_history":["I guessed."],"response_history":["Sometimes"],"rt":18250,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":74,"time_elapsed":2929528,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"If an element x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a  generato r under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Never","response":"Sometimes","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Sometimes"],"rt":11924,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":75,"time_elapsed":2941463,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"instructions":"We would like to ask you some questions about your background. Please press Continue to continue.","rt":2819,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":76,"time_elapsed":2944288,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your age?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"39","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["39"],"rt":3218,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":77,"time_elapsed":2947506,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What i s your level of education?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Did not graduate high school","High school diploma","Some college, no degree","Associates Degree","Bachelors Degree","Some graduate school, no degree","Masters Degree","Doctorate, M.D., etc."],"correct_response":"","response":"Masters Degree","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Masters Degree"],"rt":3067,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":78,"time_elapsed":2950574,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is the most advanced math class you've completed? If you have multiple classes and you're not sure which one is most advanced, please list them.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Calculus","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Calculus"],"rt":9018,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":79,"time_elapsed":2959593,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of modular arithmetic?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - never heard of it","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1 - never heard of it"],"rt":4745,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":80,"time_elapsed":2964338,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of a mathematical group?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - never heard of it","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1 - never heard of it"],"rt":4243,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":81,"time_elapsed":2968581,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you learned something from this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - not at all","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1 - not at all"],"rt":6839,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":82,"time_elapsed":2975421,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you understood the concepts in this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat"],"rt":13321,"trial_type":"q uestion","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":83,"time_elapsed":2988754,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Did you enjoy this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - not at all","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1 - not at all"],"rt":3358,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":84,"time_elapsed":2992118,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your gender?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Female","Male","Other"],"correct_response":"","response":"Female","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Female"],"rt":2614,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":85,"time_elapsed":2994733,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is/are your native language(s)? (The languages spoken in your household when you were a child.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"English","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["English"],"rt":5721,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":86,"time_elapsed":3000455,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Did you use pen and paper at any point on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"yes, as mentioned, I am not that sophisticated. I had to write out all the elements to even try to understand this stuff.","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["yes, as mentioned, I am not that sp","yes, as mentioned, I am not that sooph","yes, as mentioned, I am not that soop","yes, as mentioned, I am not that soo","yes, as mentioned, I am not that sophisticated ","yes, as mentioned, I am not that sophisticated. I had to write out all the elements to even try to understand this stuff."],"rt":26852,"trial_type":"qu estion","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":87,"time_elapsed":3027308,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you have any comments on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"I don't know how the layperson non-mathematician was supposed to follow all of this. It's frustrating.","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["I rel","I re","I r","I don't khow w","I don't khow ","I don't khow","I don't kho","I don't kh","I don't know how the layperson non-mathematician was supposed to follow all of this. It's frustrating."],"rt":37155,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":88,"time_elapsed":3064464,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"}]